# **CARLOS GUZMAN**

## **FULLSTACK DEVELOPER**

## CONTACT

- +57 3116236803
- Pereira/Risaralda Colombia
- carlosdanielgr.github.io/portfolio

## PROFESSIONAL PROFILE

Angular specialist with 3 years of experience developing robust applications. With knowledge in backend using NestJS and Laravel, I have created full-stack applications integrating Angular and NestJS, implementing file management and full CRUDs, always following development best practices.

## **EDUCATION**

### 2017 - 2019 CIAF HIGHER EDUCATION

• Software development technician

## 2023 - 2024 CIAF HIGHER EDUCATION

Software technology

# SKILLS

- Angular
- React
- Nestjs-Nodejs-Express
- MySql-PostgresSQL
- MongoDB
- Docker
- PHP-Laravel

# LANGUAGES

Spanish: NativeEnglish: Intermediate

# **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### **Innovating Solutions**

2023 - 2024

Frontend Developer

- I was part of a team developing a robust medical self-management system with Angular.
- I created modules from scratch, applying good development practices.
- I provided support to optimize and improve code performance.
- I developed reusable components, functions and services, standardizing the application.
- I migrated and refactored old code, improving its functionality.
- I solved technical problems, contributing to system stability.

#### **Betenlace SAS**

2021 - 2023

#### Frontend Developer

- I designed and structured the frontend for the startup's projects with Angular.
- Provided technical support to frontend and backend developers and reviewed PRs in Git.
- Acted as technical interviewer for aspiring frontend developers.
- Provided support to projects in production.
- Performed pair programming with new developers for their integration.
- · Collaborated with QA on user testing.
- · Documented code and key processes.
- I participated in the resolution of technical issues, development of new features and definition of timelines.